Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Public Relations records, 1934-1999 and undated RL.11700
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Events and Activities, 1972-1995 and undated; 3
  - Thompson Night--James Carville/Mary Matalin, 1993 (Box 23)
  - Thompson Night--Jeanne Kirkpatrick, 1991 (Box 23)
  - Thompson Night--John Kenneth Galbraith, 1991 (Box 23)
  - Thompson Night--Tom Kean, 1989 (Box 23)
  - Thompson Night--Tom Wolfe, 1989 (Box 23)
  - Thompson Night--William Simon, 1990 (Box 23)
  - UNICEF telethon, 1975 (Box 23)
  - United Fund drive, 1973-1974 (Box 23)
  - U.S. Bicentennial, 1973 (Box 23)
  - Winter Olympics, 1988 (Box 23)
  - With All Deliberate Speed (American Parade television program starring Paul Winfield), 1976 (Box 23)
  - WPP takeover, 1987; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - WPP takeover, 1987 (Box 24)
  - Wrestling--J. Walter Mania, 1985; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - YWCA Leadership Awards, 1980 (Box 24)
- Organizations, Offices, Subsidiaries, 1955-1996 and undated; 4
  - Ambassador International Cultural Foundation, 1975 (Box 24)
  - American Advertising Federation (AAF), 1975-1976 (Box 24)
  - AMI (Advertising and Marketing Intelligence), 1980 (Box 24)
  - AMRB (Axiom Marketing Research Bureau), 1973-1974; 3 folders (Box 24)
  - APCU-Thompson (Guatemala), 1975 (Box 24)
  - Association of National Advertisers (ANA), 1976-1978 (Box 24)
  - Brouillard Communications, 1980-1982; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Cable Shop, 1982-1983; 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Cable Shop pilot test review, 1982 (Box 24)
  - Citizens Caucus for Mass Transit, 1974 (Box 24)
  - Coalition on Organ Donations, 1992 (Box 24)
  - Communispond, 1976 (Box 24)
  - Correspondence from JWT offices, 1973-1974 (Box 24)
  - Deltakos (see also JWT Healthcare), 1972-1974; 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Dentsu, 1973-1974; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Dialog, 1973-1975; 5 folders (Box 24)
  - Eastern Airlines--Personalized vacation plans, 1974 (Box 24)
  - ED-95 agency (Netherlands), 1979 (Box 24)
  - Ferguson Communications, 1993 (Box 24)
  - Find/SVP, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Foote, Cone, Belding, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Groupaction, 1996 (Box 24)
  - Hill and Knowlton, 1980-1986; 11 folders (Box 25)
  - Hill and Knowlton--History, 1986 (Box 25)
  - Hindustan Thompson, 1981, 1994-1995; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Hispania, 1980-1986; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Institutional Development Corporation--Project Propinquity, 1975-1977 (Box 25)
  - Interlease, 1979 (Box 25)
  - Interpublic, 1985 (Box 25)
  - J. Walter Boutique (Linda Kaplan), 1987 (Box 25)
  - Jack Anderson (columnist), 1972-1973 (Box 25)
  - JWT Affiliated Companies, 1974-1975 (Box 25)
  - JWT Argentina, 1979-1980 (Box 25)
  - JWT Asia-Pacific, 1994 (Box 25)
  - JWT Atlanta/Washington, 1986 (Box 25)
  - JWT Barcelona, 1994 (Box 25)
  - JWT Board of Directors, 1985-1987, 1995; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - JWT Brazil, 1982 (Box 25)
  - JWT Chicago, 1974-1995; 7 folders (Box 25)
  - JWT Chicago--Clippings, 1972-1979; 3 folders (Box 25)
  - JWT Chicago--Clippings, 1978 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - JWT Chicago--Communications plan, 1992 (Box 26)
  - JWT Chicago--Media publicity, 1989 (Box 26)
  - JWT Denver, 1992-1993 (Box 26)
  - JWT Detroit, 1974-1994; 5 folders (Box 26)
  - JWT Detroit--Frequently asked questions, 1992 (Box 26)
  - JWT Detroit--Press kit, 1992 (Box 26)
  - JWT Direct (see also Soskin/Thompson), 1986-1993 (Box 26)
  - JWT Educational Service--Skilled Techniques in Guiding Group Action newsletter, 1955-1960 (Box 26)
  - JWT Entertainment Group, 1978 (Box 26)
  - JWT Entertainment Group, 1978 (Box 36)
  - JWT Europe, 1991-1995; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - JWT Financial Data Center, 1979 (Box 26)
  - JWT France, 1995 (Box 26)
  - JWT France--Poster, 1995 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - JWT Frankfurt, 1977, 1990-1994; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - JWT Global Media Research Group, 1995 (Box 26)
  - JWT Greece, 1993 (Box 26)
  - JWT Group, 1979-1986; 5 folders (Box 26)
  - JWT Group--Facts and organization, 1986 (Box 26)
  - JWT Group--Financial, 1983; 3 folders (Box 26)
  - JWT Group--Management succession, 1986; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - JWT Group--Mergers and acquisitions, 1986 (Box 26)
  - JWT Group--Organization chart, 1986 (Box 26)
  - JWT Group--Recent Events, 1982; 5 folders (Box 26)
  - JWT Group--WPP merger, 1987 (Box 26)
  - JWT Group (UK), 1975-1983; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - JWT Healthcare (see also Deltakos), 1986-1994; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - JWT/i.e. (interactive enterprise), 1995 (Box 26)
  - JWT Indianapolis, 1974-1977 (Box 26)
  - JWT Information Technology Group, 1996 (Box 26)
  - JWT Latin America, 1993 (Box 27)
  - JWT legal clippings, 1979 (Box 27)
  - JWT London, 1980 (Box 27)
  - JWT London--History, 1984 (Box 27)
  - JWT London Marketing Group, 1995-1996 (Box 27)
  - JWT Los Angeles, 1973-1993; 3 folders (Box 27)
  - JWT Mexico, 1977 (Box 27)
  - JWT Miami, 1980 (Box 27)
  - JWT Milan, 1986 (Box 27)
  - JWT Montreal, 1992 (Box 27)
  - JWT Moscow, 1994-1995 (Box 27)
  - JWT New York, 1974-1991; 4 folders (Box 27)
  - JWT New York--New telephone number, 1976 (Box 27)
  - JWT New York--PR plan, 1992 (Box 27)
  - JWT Omaha, 1980 (Box 27)
  - JWT OnLine, 1992 (Box 27)
  - JWT Phoenix, 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - JWT Public Relations, 1977 (Box 27)
  - JWT Research and Planning, 1977 (Box 27)
  - JWT Rome/Milan, 1993-1994 (Box 27)
  - JWT San Francisco, 1974-1994; 3 folders (Box 27)
  - JWT/Shanghai Advertising (China), 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - JWT South Africa, 1986-1987 (Box 27)
  - JWT Syndication, 1982; 3 folders (Box 27)
  - JWT Syndication--Captain Kangaroo (Slim Goodbody health segment), 1978-1979; 2 folders (Box 27)
  - JWT Syndication--Clippings, 1978 (Box 27)
  - JWT Syndication--J. Walter Thompson's Toughest Campaign (Sherry Siegel), 1982 (Box 27)
  - JWT Syndication--Kenneth and Company (women's beauty and lifestyle program), 1979 (Box 27)
  - JWT Syndication--Light from Blackness, 1975 (Box 27)
  - JWT Syndication--Materials for NATPE Conference, 1980 (Box 27)
  - JWT Syndication--Miss Peach (children's program), 1979 (Box 27)
  - JWT Syndication--NATPE press coverage, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - JWT Syndication--News releases and press, 1977-1982; 5 folders (Box 27)
  - JWT Syndication--News releases and press, 1975-1982; 3 folders (Box 28)
  - JWT Syndication--Program promotion, 1976 (Box 28)
  - JWT Syndication--Sports Special of the Month, 1974 (Box 36)
  - JWT Taiwan, 1992 (Box 35)
  - JWT Taiwan/Hong Kong, 1988 (Box 28)
  - JWT Tokyo, 1980 (Box 28)
  - JWT Toronto, 1980, 1991-1994; 2 folders (Box 28)
  - JWT Toronto, 1980 (Box 36)
  - JWT Toronto--Cassie (Canadian Advertising Success Stories) Awards, 1993 (Box 35)
  - JWT Toronto--Readers Digest Pegasus Awards, 1994 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - JWT UK clippings, 1982 (Box 28)
  - JWT USA, 1980-1981 (Box 28)
  - JWT USA--J. Walter Proud house ad, 1984 (Box 36)
  - JWT Washington, 1973-1987; 2 folders (Box 28)
  - JWT/West, 1981 (Box 28)
  - JWT World Gallery (Michael Lawrence), 1979 (Box 28)
  - JWT worldwide office addresses, 1992 (Box 28)
  - Lansdowne Advertising, 1978-1982; 2 folders (Box 28)
  - League of Public Agencies, 1975-1978 (Box 28)
  - Live Picture Network, 1996 (Box 28)
  - Lord Geller Federico and Partners, undated (Box 28)
  - Lord Geller Federico Einstein, 1980-1983 (Box 28)
  - Lord Geller Federico Peterson, 1971-1973 (Box 28)
  - Magnet Interactive Studios, 1995; 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Malcolm Green Advertising (Hong Kong), 1977 (Box 28)
  - Manajans Reklam Isleri (Turkey), 1985 (Box 28)
  - Marti Flores Prieto (Puerto Rico), 1978 (Box 28)
  - MRB International, 1979 (Box 28)
  - N.W. Ayer, 1980 (Box 28)
  - Needham, Harper and Steers, 1980 (Box 28)
  - Needham, Harper and Steers--"Fresh Stuff" portfolio, 1980-1981 (Box 35)
  - Ogilvy and Mather, 1968-1987; 3 folders (Box 28)
  - PPGH Amsterdam, 1994-1995 (Box 28)
  - Regional Advertising Group, 1993 (Box 28)
  - Simmons Research Bureau (SMRB), 1978-1982 (Box 28)
  - Soskin/Thompson (see also JWT Direct), 1979-1985; 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Speakers Bureau, 1977 (Box 28)
  - Special Correspondents (high school, student newspaper, youth market services), 1965 (Box 28)
  - Spot Advertising (Greece), 1975 (Box 28)
  - Stein Schjaevern (Sweden), 1980 (Box 28)
  - Television/Radio Age, 1984 (Box 28)
  - Thomas Cook, 1976 (Box 28)
  - Thompson Recruitment (World Wide Agency), 1979-1982; 3 folders (Box 28)
  - Tracy Locke, 1976 (Box 28)
  - WPP, 1988-1990 (Box 28)
  - WPP Group, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
  - Yeoward Taylor and Bonner (UK), 1979 (Box 28)
  - Young and Rubicam, undated (Box 28)
- Staff, 1963-1996 and undated; 5
  - 4-H interns, 1977 (Box 29)
  - Alan Anderson, 1977 (Box 29)
  - Alan Torreano, 1976 (Box 29)
  - Alfred Jarrin, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Alun Jones--Interview with Frank Mainero, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Alvin Achenbaum--Interview, 1972 (Box 29)
  - Arnold Grisman, 1980-1985 (Box 29)
  - Arnold Grisman--Desensitization of America, 1975 (Box 29)
  - Arnold Grisman--Interview with Frank Mainero, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Arnold Grisman--Letter to a Small Country, undated (Box 29)
  - Arnold Grisman--The 1980s: An Advertising Perspective, undated (Box 29)
  - Arnold Grisman--Trouble at Credibility Gap, 1974 (Box 29)
  - Arnold Grisman, Gene Secunda--Interview, 1972 (Box 29)
  - Barbara Hauptfuhrer, 1977 (Box 29)
  - Barbara Najarian--Sex discrimination suit, 1983 (Box 29)
  - Bernard Owett, 1975 (Box 29)
  - Bernie Dowling, 1982 (Box 29)
  - Bert Metter, 1982-1987 (Box 29)
  - Bert Metter--Congratulations letter on Video Storyboard Test, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Bert Metter--Interview, 1975 (Box 29)
  - Bill Petty, Michael Tremper, 1977 (Box 29)
  - Bill Ross, 1980-1981 (Box 29)
  - Bill Ross--Interview with Frank Mainero, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Bill Ross, Denis Lanigan, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Bob Irvine, 1976 (Box 29)
  - Bob Wright, 1976 (Box 29)
  - Burt Manning, 1975-1987; 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Burt Manning--Board of Directors presentation, 1984 (Box 29)
  - Burt Manning--CAB conference, 1984 (Box 29)
  - Burt Manning--Interview, 1972 (Box 29)
  - Burt Manning--Interview with Frank Mainero, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Burt Manning--Note on Miller beer, 1984 (Box 29)
  - Burt Manning--Press coverage, 1983-1986 (Box 29)
  - Burt Manning--Speeches, 1994 (Box 29)
  - Burt Manning--What Advertising Must Do in an Age of Suspicion, undated (Box 29)
  - Burt Peterson, 1981-1986 (Box 29)
  - Byron Hackett, 1975-1979 (Box 29)
  - Caroline Diehl, William Hennessy, 1977 (Box 29)
  - Charles Martell, 1982 (Box 29)
  - Charles Raymond--Recollections of early JWT, 1943 (Box 29)
  - Charles Rheinstrom obituary, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Charlotte Beers, 1973 (Box 29)
  - Charlotte Strouse obituary, 1982 (Box 29)
  - Clipping file, 1982; 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Colin Dawkins obituary, 1986 (Box 29)
  - Cynthia Krimezis, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Dan Seymour, 1963-1982 (Box 29)
  - Dan Seymour--Interview, 1972 (Box 29)
  - David Murphy, 1975 (Box 29)
  - David Murphy--Difficulties in Media Planning, 1977 (Box 29)
  - Dean Thie, 1977 (Box 29)
  - Denis Lanigan, 1982 and undated; 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Denis Lanigan--Interview, 1972 (Box 29)
  - Denis Lanigan--Interview with Frank Mainero, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Dennis Altman, Ed Hiestand, 1977 (Box 29)
  - Dennis McCart, 1982 (Box 29)
  - Denton Cruse, 1982 (Box 29)
  - Derry Daly obituary, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Dione Guffey, 1976 (Box 29)
  - Don Brown, 1984 (Box 29)
  - Don Deaton, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Don Johnston, 1974-1982; 3 folders (Box 29)
  - Don Johnston--Clippings, 1979-1981 (Box 29)
  - Don Johnston--Interview, 1972 (Box 29)
  - Don Johnston--Interview in India, 1980-1981 (Box 29)
  - Don Johnston--Interview with Frank Mainero, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Don Johnston--Interview with William Whytte, 1978; 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Don Johnston--Speeches, 1979-1981 (Box 29)
  - Don Robertson (JWT Canada), 1980 (Box 29)
  - Don Robertson (JWT Canada)--Interview, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Don Sullivan, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Don Thompson, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Donald Ayers, 1986 (Box 29)
  - Donald Washburn--Design for Action, Decisions under Uncertainty, 1965 (Box 29)
  - Donald Washburn--Women in a Changing American Food Market, 1966 (Box 29)
  - Dorothy Marcus, 1991-1996 (Box 29)
  - Dorothy Philips, Wesley Hostetler, 1977 (Box 29)
  - E. Wyatte Hicks, 1973-1974 (Box 30)
  - E. Wyatte Hicks, Gene Secunda--Interview, 1972 (Box 30)
  - Ed Hiestand, Ludwig Dochtermann, 1986 (Box 30)
  - Edith Gilson, 1984-1987 (Box 30)
  - Edward (Ed) Haymes, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Edward B. (Ted) Wilson, 1974-1976 (Box 30)
  - Edward B. (Ted) Wilson--Interview, 1972 (Box 30)
  - Edward Lambek, 1975 (Box 30)
  - Elizabeth (Betty) Harrigan (includes lawsuit), 1972-1979 (Box 30)
  - Ernest Emerling, Tom Yamada, 1977 (Box 30)
  - Executive biographies, 1986 (Box 30)
  - Executive changes, 1977 (Box 30)
  - Executive profiles, 1987 (Box 30)
  - Farlan Myers, 1975 (Box 30)
  - Frank Mainero, 1977 (Box 30)
  - Frank Nicolo, 1977 (Box 30)
  - Frank Stanton, 1987 (Box 30)
  - Gabriel Samuels, 1976-1982 (Box 30)
  - Gene Secunda, 1977-1980 (Box 30)
  - Gene Secunda, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Gene Secunda--Government advertising expenditures, undated (Box 30)
  - George Black, 1981 (Box 30)
  - George Black, Burkhard Schwarz, 1977 (Box 30)
  - George Clements, 1993 (Box 30)
  - George Eversman, 1974-1977 (Box 30)
  - Gerald Broderick, 1977 (Box 30)
  - Glen Dell, 1986 (Box 30)
  - Glen Fortinberry, 1976-1980 (Box 30)
  - Glen Fortinberry--Interview with Frank Mainero, 1978 (Box 30)
  - Greg Bathon, 1982 (Box 30)
  - Greg Bathon--Interview with Frank Mainero, 1977 (Box 30)
  - H.J. Barnum (includes lawsuit), 1975 (Box 30)
  - Harry Clark, 1974-1984 (Box 30)
  - Harvard Business School alumni, 1973 (Box 30)
  - Henry Curtis obituary, 1986 (Box 30)
  - Henry Davis, 1976 (Box 30)
  - Henry Flower obituary, 1984 (Box 30)
  - Henry Schachte, 1972-1974 (Box 30)
  - Henry Schachte--Interview, 1972 (Box 30)
  - Henry Simmons, 1975 (Box 30)
  - Herbert Eames, 1980 (Box 30)
  - Herman Coenan (JWT Amsterdam), 1975 (Box 30)
  - Howard Brundage--Interview, 1972 (Box 30)
  - Hugh Connell, 1977-1982 (Box 30)
  - Hugh Connell--Interview with Frank Mainero, 1978 (Box 30)
  - Hugh Connell, Gene Secunda--Interview, 1972 (Box 30)
  - Jack Cronin, 1977-1987 (Box 30)
  - Jack Stevens, 1977 (Box 30)
  - James (Jim) Agnew, 1982 (Box 30)
  - James (Jim) Heekin, 1987 (Box 30)
  - James Kennedy, 1982 (Box 30)
  - James Patterson, 1977-1988 (Box 30)
  - James Patterson, Andrew Romano, 1977 (Box 30)
  - Jean Miller, 1975-1977 (Box 30)
  - Jean Pool, 1987 (Box 30)
  - Jeanne Maraz, 1976 (Box 30)
  - Jeremy Bullmore (JWT London), 1975-1977 (Box 30)
  - Jeremy Bullmore (JWT London)--Interview, 1972 (Box 30)
  - Jim Willette, 1981 (Box 30)
  - Joel Baumwoll, 1975-1976 (Box 30)
  - John Barnhill, 1977 (Box 30)
  - John Becker, 1982 (Box 30)
  - John Cox, 1979 (Box 30)
  - John (Jack) Devine, Gene Secunda--Interview, 1972 (Box 30)
  - John Gray, 1984 (Box 30)
  - John McQuigg obituary, 1982 (Box 30)
  - John Nason, 1977 (Box 30)
  - John Sharman (JWT Australia)--Interview, 1972 (Box 30)
  - John Sharman (JWT Australia)--Interview with Frank Mainero, 1978 (Box 30)
  - John Spillner, 1977 (Box 30)
  - John Treasure (JWT London), 1973-1975 (Box 30)
  - John Treasure (JWT London)--Interview, 1972 (Box 30)
  - Jon Tracosas, 1982 (Box 30)
  - Joseph Boyle obituary, 1976 (Box 30)
  - Joseph Brouillard (English and French), 1975-1978 (Box 30)
  - Joseph (Joe) O'Donnell, 1984-1986 (Box 30)
  - Joseph (Joe) O'Donnell, Merrill Snyder, 1977 (Box 30)
  - JWT Board of Directors biographies, 1981 (Box 30)
  - JWT USA Board of Directors, undated (Box 30)
  - Karen Maher, Robert Losi, 1987 (Box 30)
  - Ken Fairchild, 1977 (Box 30)
  - Kennett Webb Hinks obituary, 1982 (Box 30)
  - Kyo Takahashi, 1973 (Box 30)
  - Larry Olshan, 1976-1982 (Box 30)
  - Lee Pavao, 1977 (Box 30)
  - Lee Pratt, 1977 (Box 30)
  - Lee Preschel, 1987 (Box 30)
  - Lee Preschel, Lee Pavao, 1987 (Box 30)
  - Linda Loose, 1987 (Box 30)
  - Lois Papale, 1982 (Box 30)
  - Loy Baxter, with son Jeff "Skunk" Baxter, 1975 (Box 30)
  - Marie Luisi, 1977-1984 (Box 30)
  - Marie Luisi--New Media speech, 1981 (Box 30)
  - Mark Hallen--Book announcement, 1987 (Box 30)
  - Michael Cooper-Evans, Miles Colebrook, 1984 (Box 30)
  - Miscellaneous photographs of staff, 1986-1987 and undated; 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Miscellaneous speeches, 1963-1977 (Box 30)
  - Nariman Dhalla, 1975-1977 (Box 31)
  - Pat McMillan, undated (Box 31)
  - Pat Moran, 1977-1980 (Box 31)
  - Peggy Yervanian, 1982 (Box 31)
  - Peter Gilow (JWT Germany), Rene Muller (JWT Switerland)--Interview, 1972 (Box 31)
  - Peter Gridley, 1981 (Box 31)
  - Peter Mills, Wally O'Brien, 1979-1982 (Box 31)
  - Peter Schweitzer, 1976-1981 (Box 31)
  - Peter Schweitzer, Joe Schulte, 1986 (Box 31)
  - Professional Development Program, 1986-1987 (Box 31)
  - Promotions news releases, 1975-1987; 4 folders (Box 31)
  - R.E. (Buck) Buchanan, 1975-1982 (Box 31)
  - R.E. (Buck) Buchanan--Retirement, 1985 (Box 31)
  - R.E. (Buck) Buchanan--Television Program Content: Violence, 1977 (Box 31)
  - Ram Ray, 1982 (Box 31)
  - Raymond Fragrasso, 1976 (Box 31)
  - Rena Bartos, 1975-1982 (Box 31)
  - Rena Bartos--Over 40: The Invisible Consumer Market, 1980 (Box 31)
  - Richard (Dick) Jones, 1964-1976 (Box 31)
  - Richard Kostyra, 1986 (Box 31)
  - Richard Rasor, 1975 (Box 31)
  - Robert Gray, 1983-1984 (Box 31)
  - Robert King, 1976 (Box 31)
  - Robert Roche obituary, 1977 (Box 31)
  - Robert Selby, 1987 (Box 31)
  - Robert Zimmern, 1977 (Box 31)
  - Robin Restall, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Rolf Meise, 1984 (Box 32)
  - Ron Burns, 1977-1991 (Box 32)
  - Ron Burns--130th anniversary speech, 1994 (Box 32)
  - Ron Kaatz, 1975-1981 (Box 32)
  - Ron Kaatz--In Search of What the Ratings Hide, 1985 (Box 32)
  - Ron Kovas, 1983 (Box 32)
  - Ron Sherman, 1980 (Box 32)
  - Ron Sherman--Interview with Frank Mainero, 1978 (Box 32)
  - Roy Glah, 1977-1987 (Box 32)
  - Sam Meek, 1964-1967 (Box 32)
  - Sam Meek obituary, 1981 (Box 32)
  - Sonia Yuspeh, 1982 (Box 32)
  - Stephen Salorio, 1980-1984 (Box 32)
  - Stephen Vengrove, Alan Webb, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Steve Bowen, 1984-1988 (Box 32)
  - Summaries of interviews with JWT executives, 1972 (Box 32)
  - Susan Mirsky, 1986 (Box 32)
  - Terry Valeski, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Thurman Pierce, 1976-1986 (Box 32)
  - Tom Greer, 1982 (Box 32)
  - Tom Hall, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Tom Robbins, 1984 (Box 32)
  - Tom Sutton--Interview, 1972 (Box 32)
  - Tom Veres, 1980-1981 (Box 32)
  - Walter (Wally) O'Brien, 1982-1986 (Box 32)
  - Wayne Fickinger, 1978-1980 (Box 32)
  - Wayne Fickinger--Interview with Frank Mainero, 1978 (Box 33)
  - Wayne Fickinger, Denis Lanigan, 1981-1982 (Box 33)
  - Wayne Fickinger, Gene Secunda--Interview, 1972 (Box 33)
  - Wendell Pope, 1977 (Box 33)
  - William (Bill) Cameron, 1974 (Box 33)
  - William (Bill) Lane, 1977 (Box 33)
  - William Nye, 1974 (Box 33)
  - William Peniche, 1976 (Box 33)
  - William Sharfman, 1982 (Box 33)
  - William Thompson, 1979-1987 (Box 33)
  - William (Bill) Williams, 1987 (Box 33)
  - Wilson Seibert--3 Great Periods of Creative Advertising, 1978 (Box 33)
  - Wilson Seibert--Interview, 1972 (Box 33)
  - Wolfgang Lieschke, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Worldwide officers addresses, 1991 (Box 33)